Male Speaker: So, we need to plan a special day for Alex.
What do you think?
Female Speaker: How about going to the cinema?
Alex loves the cinema, and we can choose a film he likes.
Male Speaker: I’m not sure about that.
We want to talk and laugh with Alex.
We can’t do that in the cinema.
Female Speaker: That’s true.
Male Speaker: We need to think of a special activity –
something we don’t do every day.
What about going to an escape room?
Female Speaker: I don’t think that’s a very good idea.
Male Speaker: Why’s that?
Female Speaker: Escape rooms are very expensive.
Also, they’re only for one or two hours.
We want to spend all day with Alex.
Male Speaker: You’re right.
Female Speaker: I know!
How about having a picnic in the country.
It isn’t expensive and we can stay all day.
Male Speaker: That’s a great idea!
We can take our own lunch, too –
for example, sandwiches and salads.
Female Speaker: Yes, and we can do a lot of things like go for a walk or play games.
Male Speaker: We can have the picnic next weekend.
Female Speaker: Great! Let’s make a list of Alex’s friends.
We can send them a group invitation.